I went shopping at the supermarket and came home.
A lovely soap I received as a gift.
I couldn't use it for a long time because it's too cute.
It was the perfect weekend treat!
I read a book the other day.
It said something like, "Sleep 8 hours, work 8 hours, commute 2 hours, what do you do with the rest of your time?
(My memory is a little hazy.) I read something like that.
I used to look forward to watching dramas at night for dinner and on my days off.
influenced by the book.
I decided to try to watch drama only one day a week.
I'm really happy because today I can finally lift the ban on all the dramas that I've been keeping under wraps.
Here are today's purchases.
I pre-frozen some chicken for deep frying.
I'm all set to watch the drama.
I'm watching a Korean drama right now.
I'm going to make a Korean style dinner and enjoy the drama as much as I can... 🤭.
While the chicken is defrosting
I wash my soiled bag.
I'm watching a drama that has become a once a week thing.
I have to take my time and enjoy it.
I'm starving, so I'm going to have a snack and
I'm going to finish chores.
crackers given by a friend.
and some Kagoshima rice cakes I found at the Kyushu fair at the train station.
It has brown sugar in it and is sweet and delicious 🤤.
I love it so much I took it home with me to treasure 🍘.
Socks covered in furballs
I turned on the switch.
I gathered up all the furball socks
I like to watch the harvest.🐀
I clean up the dishes and make a movie night dinner set.
I'm going to remove the sand from the clam for tomorrow's breakfast
I make a green onion salad with a lot of green onions.
(recipe by Mr. heungsam)
Recipe for plenty of onions and scallions
(Recipe by delicious day's channnel)
Garlic
Canned tuna, drained of oil
1 tbs of gochujang (red pepper paste), 0.5 each of mirin and sugar, 2 tbs of water
Rice and sesame leaves as it is
It's very tasty with a lot of sesame leaves
Made with sesame oil and sesame seeds
Chicken seasoned with salt kouji
Coated with a 1:1 ratio of potato starch and flour
I also made tteokbokki from Kaldi's
salt, sugar, vinegar, and powdered chili pepper to taste
Simple but very tasty!
Happy holiday combo... 🍟🍗
The fun moment I've been waiting for
I thought I was going to have withdrawal symptoms lol
I could look forward to this time and work hard
And more love for the drama lol.
It was a very good way
I'm going to take a bath first.
I'm going to finish cleaning up quickly.
Now that the weather is warming up
I change to a refreshing skin care
The remaining veins can be used for interior decoration
As the Golden Week is approaching
I end up watching videos of international travel
I brush my teeth and go to bed
Dessert I wanted to make
It looks easy to make, so I'm going to make it before breakfast.
400g milk, 30g sugar, 10g gelatin, vanilla essence
Harden in refrigerator
240g water, 20g sugar, 2 butterfly peas tea
350ml of peach milk base with carbonated water
Dissolve 5g of gelatin in 2 tbs of hot water and add
Wrap jelly that needs no container
I found a recipe for burdock and mitsuba and I'm going to make it for breakfast
I'm going to boil the mitsuba quickly
1/2 ts white soup stock, 1/2 ts sugar, 1/2 tbs vinegar, 1/2 tbs soy sauce, 2 tbs ground sesame seeds
Sesame paste with mitsuba and burdock root.
Egg, a pinch of salt
Kimbap with rice that has become a little hard.
Wrap it with egg and warm it up
Put frozen shijimi with water directly into the pot
1/4 ts amount of chicken broth, a pinch of salt
Cheese savory
I will have it while listening to the radio
I have plans for dinner at night.
I'm going to leave early and go see the cherry blossoms
I used a transparent case as a pouch
On a day when it was 25 degrees Celsius
I almost didn't wear the jacket I had so much trouble choosing 😅
I came to Nakameguro where the cherry blossom festival was held.
but the cherry blossoms were still too early 🤭.
I came here to choose a present for a friend of mine
There are so many kinds of Japanese and Western stlye tableware
There are so many things I want...
I have to take this dog only 🐕.
microwave and dishwasher safe dishes for my friend.
I wanted to try the bain-mee,
but they were sold out😅
I came to a soup noodle store with rice noodles called mee sheng!
I also have a mixed drink of tea and coffee.
It was delicious and spicy, perfect for the summer-like weather!
To Odaiba where we are going to meet.
It looks like we can see the sunset
The sky here and the view of Tokyo on the other side of the sea always makes me feel refreshed.
It didn't make a beautiful gradation,
It is enough that it solidified 🤭.
I really liked the combination of peach jelly and milk jelly💗.
March 31st was the day I moved to Tokyo for the first time, so it was a week that reminded me of many things.
How was your week? 🌸💗
Thank you for watching to the end!